everypixel.com 2011-01-30

# Pixim | Privacy

## Privacy Policy

Pixim Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information collection and use practices for our web site. We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process. 

**Use of Cookies**

We may use "cookies" to help create a more effective and convenient site experience. By showing us how and when visitors use the site, "cookies" help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on data such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. Pixim Inc. does not store any sensitive information in the cookie. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Pixim Inc. may ask you to provide certain personal information about yourself such as name, address, e-mail address, phone number, purchase details, and other personally identifying information. This information may be requested to: enable you to request a demo, white paper, or other collateral; sign up for a seminar; register a product; request support; ask Pixim Inc. to contact you; participate in Pixim Inc.'s on-line programs, communities or promotions; or to allow Pixim Inc. to provide updates and information and/or support regarding its products and services, send electronic newsletters, respond to user inquiries and requests for information, provide information on educational events, enable joint sales or product promotions (with Pixim Inc. partners), enable your participation in interactive discussions and public forums, or as a result of legal requirements. 

Participation is completely optional. Continued use of some of the features on our website(s), however, may be conditioned upon providing such personal information. If you elect to give us your personal information over the Internet, Pixim Inc. will take reasonable precautions to ensure the security of your information including using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window. When contacting us for technical or customer support, your e-mail address will be used to respond to your query. In some cases, we may invite you to participate in an online survey to let us know how we are doing. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Pixim Inc. does not embed advertising (adware) in any of our software. This site contains links to other sites; Pixim Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. By using our site, you agree to this Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change it by posting a new version on our site. This site operates as-is and as available. Any warranties of accuracy, quality, title, fitness or merchantability are disclaimed. We are not liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damages, or for events beyond our direct control. 

California law governs this Policy, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any provision of this Policy that is illegal or unenforceable shall be deemed automatically conformed to the minimum requirements of law. 

**CONTACTING Pixim Inc.**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact: 

Pixim Inc., Inc.   
1395 Charleston Rd.   
Mountain View, CA 94043   
Phone: 650-934-0550   
Fax: 650-934-0560
